<resources>
    <string name="web_search_prompt_news_guidance">Use the host-provided %1$s tool for current information. Do not invent current facts, dates, sources, URLs, weather, prices, schedules, or news. If search results are empty, irrelevant, or failed, say that the information could not be confirmed. The latest user message matches a news/current-events intent. You must call %1$s before answering. The host may send the factual news summary directly from tool results. After tool results are available, do not repeat news items, dates, sources, or URLs. Provide only a brief evaluation or commentary on the confirmed news in the configured persona.</string>
    <string name="web_search_prompt_weather_guidance">Use the host-provided %1$s tool for current information. Do not invent current facts, dates, sources, URLs, weather, prices, schedules, or news. If search results are empty, irrelevant, or failed, say that the information could not be confirmed. The latest user message asks for weather or other live conditions. You must call %1$s before answering and base the answer only on returned sources.</string>
    <string name="web_search_prompt_realtime_guidance">Use the host-provided %1$s tool for current information. Do not invent current facts, dates, sources, URLs, weather, prices, schedules, or news. If search results are empty, irrelevant, or failed, say that the information could not be confirmed. The latest user message appears to require current or live information. Prefer calling %1$s before answering.</string>
    <string name="web_search_prompt_direct_delivery_status_sent">sent</string>
    <string name="web_search_prompt_direct_delivery_status_failed">failed</string>
    <string name="web_search_prompt_news_direct_delivery_commentary">The factual news summary has already been sent to the user by the host.\nDirect delivery status: %1$s.\nSent summary:\n%2$s\n\nDo not repeat the news items, sources, dates, URLs, or numeric details. Only provide a brief evaluation or commentary in the configured persona. If the summary says no confirmed news was found, evaluate that uncertainty and do not invent facts.</string>
</resources>
